<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://lancewilhelm.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://lancewilhelm.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2023-05-08T00:01:32+00:00</updated><id>https://lancewilhelm.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Lance T. Wilhelm</title><subtitle>A academic portfolio website for Lance T. Wilhelm, United States Air Force Captain.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Embracing New Horizons</title><link href="https://lancewilhelm.github.io/blog/2023/first-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Embracing New Horizons" /><published>2023-05-07T16:44:00+00:00</published><updated>2023-05-07T16:44:00+00:00</updated><id>https://lancewilhelm.github.io/blog/2023/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://lancewilhelm.github.io/blog/2023/first-post/"><![CDATA[<p>As a new day dawns on my academic and professional journey, I can’t help but feel excited about finally creating my first academic and professional portfolio website. This website will showcase my achievements, aspirations, and experiences, reflecting my commitment to growth and transformation in the fields of computer science and AI/ML.</p>

<p>With great enthusiasm, I announce my intention to pivot my energy towards pursuing Ph.D. programs in computer science and AI/ML. This decision marks a significant step in my journey, allowing me to delve deeper into the world of algorithms, artificial neurons, and machine learning while collaborating with like-minded individuals who share my passion for discovery and innovation.</p>

<p>The creation of my portfolio website represents not only a personal milestone but also an opportunity to connect with others, share my story, and seek out new challenges. I eagerly anticipate the knowledge and experiences that lie ahead as I embark on this next phase of my academic and professional life.</p>

<p>Join me on this exciting journey as we explore the limitless possibilities of computer science and AI/ML together. The future is bright, and I am eager to see where our collective efforts will lead.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello blog world!]]></summary></entry></feed>